wantable.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated: September 22, 2014  
Effective Date: July 15, 2012

We at Wantable.com value your business, and trust. Therefore, we will not sell, rent, or give away any customers’ e-mail address to other businesses. We request your e-mail address so we can send you important information regarding your order (order confirmation, order processing, and tracking number). We may e-mail you company information, coupons, or discount offers in the future.

### Tracking

Wantable.com tracks information about the visits to the site. For example, statistics are compiled that show the daily number of visitors to the site, the daily requests received for particular files on the site, and from what countries those requests come. Wantable.com may also track information about our users browsing activity as they navigate through our site. These statistics are used to customize our Web site to better meet your needs and may also be provided to others, but we will not provide any personally identifiable information that may be associated with those statistics to any third parties.

### Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s (or other device’s) persistent storage medium (e.g., hard drive) through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. We use cookies to enhance visitors’ experiences, to learn more about their use of the Website and to improve quality. Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Website’s most attractive features. Wantable does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

Ads appearing on the Website may be delivered to users by Wantable’s advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer or other device each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer or device. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.

### Information Collection and Use

Wantable does not sell, giveaway, or rent to any customer information to outside companies.  If you provided your email to us through a sweepstakes, we may share information with directly related sweepstake sponsors.  A separate privacy policy for each sweepstake is provided explaining information use and sponsor distribution.

If logging in through Facebook, we collect and store birthdate, first name, last name, gender, location, and profile picture. Information coming from Facebook is not shared. Your Facebook account can always be unlinked to your Wantable account by emailing Wantable at [hello@wantable.com](https://www.wantable.com/support).

### iOS App

The Wantable iOS App is subject to the same Privacy Policy as our Website.

Images shared to Wantable.com through our iOS app may be displayed on our site or used on promotional materials. Images shared to Wantable.com through the iOS app will also be shown to other Wantable.com customers that have received the product tagged in the image, along with your name, username, profile image, and any biographical information you’ve provided on your Wantable app profile.

You may elect not to share a photo with Wantable.com by turning off that sharing option during the uploading process for the iOS App. Please do not publish any photos that you wish to keep private.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Wantable may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after changes have been posted.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy, please send us a detailed message at [hello@wantable.com](https://www.wantable.com/support). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
